Hunger Action Network of New York State; Records apap161
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Welfare Reform Campaigns, 1973-2000, Undated; 4; 2.66 cubic ft.
  - World Food Day, 1999 (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 10)
- Publications & Reports, 1973-2000, Undated; 5; 1.66 cubic ft.
  The Publications and Reports series is arranged chronologically.
  The publications and reports series refers to any and all publications that were collected by the Hunger Action Network of New York State and also materials that were disseminated by the organization. Many of the Hunger Action Network of New York State publications were the product of different grants that the organization had received funding through, such as the Robert Sterling Clark Foundation. The collection has many publications that have been used as reference and research points for the organization. The Hunger Action Network of New York State and its member organizations are reflected in the publications. The Hunger Action Network of New York States newsletter is part of the publication series, however there is not a complete run of this newsletter.
  - Identifying A Food Policy Agenda For The 1980s: A Working Paper, 1980 Janaury (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, Hunger Action 1984-2000 (1 of 2) (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, Hunger Action 1984-2000 (2 of 2) (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 3)
  - Message to the Legislature, 1985 Janaury 09 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 4)
  - Joint Report on Emergency Food Relief in New York State, 1985 April (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 5)
  - A Primer Of New York State Food Assistance Programs, 1986 February (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 6)
  - Hunger Notes: The National Newsletter of the National Student Campiagn Against Hunger, 1986 September (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 7)
  - Welfare Simplification: Thirty-Two States' Views on Coordinating Service for Low-Income Families, 1986 October (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 8)
  - Food Stamp Program: Evaluation of Improper Denial or Termination Error Rates, 1987 October (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 9)
  - Food With Dignity: A Study of People Using Food Pantries in New York State, 1987 October (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 10)
  - Fuel For Excellence: FRAC's Guide to School Breakfast Expansion, 1987 October (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 11)
  - It's Time For New York To Increase The Minimum Wage, 1988 May (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 12)
  - Hole In The Safety Nets: Poverty Programs And Policies In The States: New York, 1998 Spring (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 13)
  - Definitions and Reality of Poverty, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 14)
  - Statistical Supplement to the 1988 Annual Report of the New York State Department of Social Services (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 15)
  - Outreach Strategies to Increase Food Program Participation, 1989 April 26 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 16)
  - Poverty In Rural America: A National Overview, 1989 April (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 17)
  - Private Food Assistance in New York State: Challenges for the 1990s, 1989 July (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 18)
  - Job Training Partnership Act: Information on Training, Placements, and Wages of Male and Female Participants, 1989 September (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 19)
  - Activist's Guide to Religious Funders, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 20)
  - Community Service Block Grant Program: Directory of Service, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 21)
  - Losing Ground: A Decade of Homelessness Comes To A Close, And There Is No End In Sight, 1990 February (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 22)
  - The Bush Administration Budget: Rhetoric and Reality, 1990 February (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 23)
  - Asleep At The Wheel: A Study of how New York State Supervises Local Departments of Social Services, 1990 April (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 24)
  - Fuel For Excellence: FRAC's Guide to School Breakfast Expansion, Second Edition, 1990 September (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 25)
  - Tailor Made: The Earned Income Tax Credit and Hispanic Working Poor Families, 1990 September (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 26)
  - Struggle to Survive: The Plight of AFDC and Low Wage Working Families in New York, 1990 October (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 27)
  - Human Needs in Onondaga County 1990: A Status Report, 1990 November (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 28)
  - State Of Emergency: Reforming State Supervision and Local Delivery of Emergency Assistance, 1991 January (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 29)
  - Unchanged Priorities: The Fiscal Year 1992 Bush Budget, 1991 February (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 30)
  - Limited Access: Health Care for the Rural Poor, 1991 March (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 31)
  - Playing To Win: A Marshall Plan For America, 1991 July (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 32)
  - Selective Prosperity: Increasing Income Disparities Since 1977, 1991 July (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 33)
  - County Human Services Directory, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 34)
  - Food Stamps: Facts, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 35)
  - Hunger and Poverty in the United States: A High School Curriculum, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 36)
  - Hungry and Poor: The Results of the Community Childhood Hunger Identification Program (CCHIP) In Queens County, 1992 April (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 37)
  - Assesment of the Structure and Functioning of the New York State Department of Social Services: Findings, Conclusions, and Reccomendations, 1992 May (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 38)
  - The New York Child Assistance Program: Interim Report on Program Impacts, 1992 June (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 39)
  - Schenectady County Hunger Study, 1992 July (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 40)
  - Jobs & The Economy: A Primer on Principled Economic Development for Progressive Elected Officials and Activists, 1992 August (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 41)
  - Ten Years Working to End Hunger in New York State 1982-1992, 1992 October 17 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 42)
  - White Poverty In America, 1992 October (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 43)
  - New York State Nutrition: State of the State, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 44)
  - An Affordable State Medicaid Takeover, 1993 January (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 45)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy: Federal Fiscal Year 1993, 1993 February (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 46)
  - Peace Newsletter: Central New York's Voice for Peace and Social Justice, 1993 June (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 47)
  - Living At The Bottom: An Analysis of AFDC Benefit Levels, 1993 July (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 48)
  - Hunger 1994: Transforming the Politics of Hunger, 1993 October (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 49)
  - United Tenants of Albany: 20th Anniversary, 1993 (Box 1 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 50)
  - Welfare Reform: A "Jobs FIRST" Strategy, 1994 January (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 1)
  - Making the Case for a State Earned Income Tax Credit: A County by County Profile of NYS Claimants, 1994 February (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 2)
  - Speak Out For Change! Overcoming Stereotypes and Misconceptions on Hunger, Poverty, Food Stamps, and School Breakfast, 1994 March (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 3)
  - Racefile: A critical assessment of reporting on racial issues in the established and community press, 1994 May-June (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 4)
  - Facts on the Minimum Wage, 1994 June (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 5)
  - Living At The Bottom: An Analysis of AFDC Benefit Levels, 1994 June (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 6)
  - New York State Kids Count 1994 Data Book (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 7)
  - Report to Governor George E. Pataki Regarding the State Fiscal Year 1995-1996 Medicaid Budget, 1995 January 18 (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 8)
  - Poverty and Race: Poverty and Race Research Action Council Volume 4, No. 2, 1995 March-April (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 9)
  - Workfare in New York State: Does it Work?, 1995 July 12 (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 10)
  - Can New York Afford the Way Congress Intends to Balance the Federal Budget?, 1995 July (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 11)
  - Perceptions of Hunger and the Reality of Programs, 1995 July (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 12)
  - Perceptions of Hunger and the Reality of Programs, 1995 July (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 13)
  - The Impact of Federal Legislation on New York State Nutrition Programs, 1995 December (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 14)
  - Hunger Action Network of New York State (HANNYS) Welfare Reform Teach-In Packet, 1996 (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 15)
  - Public Policy/Private Pain: Reaching Consensus on Welfare Reform, 1996 (Box 2 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 16)
  - The Status of the Summer Food Service Program In Cities: 1997, 1997 April (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 1)
  - Show Her the Money: A Study of the Earned Income Disregard For Welfare Participants in New York State, 1997 May (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 2)
  - Why: Challenging Hunger and Poverty, 1997 Spring (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 3)
  - Hunger Doesn't Take A Vacation: A Status Report on the Summer Food Service Program For Children, 5th ed., 1997 July (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 4)
  - Workfare: Workers Expect Paychecks: a Snapshot Survey of the Performance of Workfare According to Participants, 1997 December (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 5)
  - Putting the "To" in "Welfare To Work": Transportation Issues and Initiatives Around Welfare Reform, 1997 (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 6)
  - The People's Budget 1998-1999: A Blueprint for Equity, 1998 January 06 (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 7)
  - Are States Improving the Lives of Poor Families? A Scale Measure of State Welfare Policies, 1998 February (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 8)
  - Learnfare: Teaching Discrimination to New York's Children, 1998 April (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 9)
  - Building an Employee Focused Welfare System: Work First and Other Work Oriented Strategies in Five States, 1998 June (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 10)
  - The People's Budget: A Blueprint for Equity, 1998 November 30 (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 11)
  - The People's Budget: A Blueprint for Equity, 1998 November 30 (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 12)
  - Living on the Edge: A Study of People Relying on Emergency Feeding Programs in the Empire State, 1998 November (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 13)
  - A Blind Eye: Assembling New York's 1999-2000 Executive Budget in Economic, Social and Fiscal Terms, 1999 February (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 14)
  - From Welfare to Well Paid Work: A Guide to Successful, Participant-Focused, Welfare Reform Programs from Across the Nation and a Progress Report on New York State's Welfare Reform Efforts, 1999 August (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 15)
  - Promising Practices in Welfare-To-Work: Positive Programs Which Can Help Move New Yorkers Up and Out of the Stranglehold of Welfare, 1999 November (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 16)
  - Putting It All Together to Create Changes, 2000 September (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 17)
  - Downside: The Human Consequences of the Giuliani Administration's Welfare Caseload Cuts, 2000 November (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 18)
  - A Community Shared Agricultural Employment Pilot Project, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 19)
  - Barriers to Health Care in Rensselaer County, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 20)
  - Bridging The Gap: Transitional Benefits - What Are They? An Overview and Survey of 15 Counties, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 21)
  - CEJ's Welfare Reform Monitoring Project Phase II Report, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 22)
  - Changing Views Of Poverty, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 23)
  - Family Income, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 24)
  - In The Shadow of the Capitol: Childhood Hunger in Washington, D.C., Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 25)
  - Speaking Out For Change: A Media Relations Road Map For Low Income People and Advocates, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 26)
  - Welfare Reform: Strategies for Successful Programs, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 27)
  - Who Are The Poor? A Profile of the Changing Faces of Poverty in the United States in 1987, Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications & Reports), Folder 28)
- Research & Subject Files, 1973-2000, Undated; 6; 4.5 cubic ft.
  The Research and Subject Files series is arranged alphabetically.
  The Research and Subject Files series contains materials of the Hunger Action Network of New York State used as background and in support of their mission. Many of the files are supplemental materials in nature. Welfare reform research is prominently featured in this series. Please note that materials related to HANNYSs welfare reform campaigns are in series 4. Subject files cover a broad perspective of the Hunger Action Network of New York State such as fundraising endeavors and direct mailings from other social reform organizations.
  - 10 for 10, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - 25th Anniversary Hope House Dinner Program, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Albany County Oppurtunity, Inc. Parent, Staff, Volunteer Dinner Program, 1992 June 22 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Ancillary Services to Support Welfare to Work, 1992 June 22 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - ARISE, 1999; 2000 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Baby Boost Program, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Breakfast Programs in Schools, 1996; 1999; Undated (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Benefit Concert to Help End Hunger, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Budget Forms, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Cable Company Contacts, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Capitaland Community Garden, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Catholic Charities, United Church of Christ, and Presbyterian Funding, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Child Assistance Program, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Child Nutrition, 1983-1987; 1993; 1996 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Childhood Hunger, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Common Agenda Coalition, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Community Farming, 2000 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Community Food, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Community Food Nutrition Program, 2001 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Community Food Project, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Community Voices Heard, 1994-1996; 1998 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Contracting, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Contracts for Food and Shelters, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Corporate Sponsors, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - CROP Hunger Walk, Undated (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - CVH Transition, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Department of Labor Welfare to Work Division, 1997; 1998; 2000 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Direct Mailings from Other Social Reform Organizations, 1990-1999; Undated (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Direct Mailings from Other Social Reform Organizations, 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Domestic Hunger/ Poverty and Economic Justice Program: Guidelines and Application for Funding, 1997-2000 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Emergency Assistance Work Group, 1986; 1990-1991 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Emergency Feeding, 1989; 1993 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Emergency Food and Shelter Program, 1996; 1999 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Evangelical Lutheran Church in America Domestic Hunger Grants Program Materials, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Faces of Welfare Reform Mock-up with Original Photographs, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Fair Budget, 1997; 1998 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Fair Budget, 1997-2001 (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Faith Community Outreach Plan, Undated (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Families USA Tax Credits for the Uninsured Report, 2001 September (Box 1 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Farmers Market, 1997-2001 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Food Shuttle and Island Harvest, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Bread for the World, 1993-1997 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Fundraising Development Action Plan, 1997 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Fundraising Iniatives, 1993; 1996; 1997 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Gardening, 1996; 2001; Undated (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Gleaning, 1994; 1996; 2001 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Graphics for HANNYS, 1996; 1998 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Grow an Extra Row, 1998 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Hamilton College Program, 2001 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - The Homeless, 1986-1998 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Hunger Fellows Programs, 1998 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Hunger Organizing Project (HOP), 1989-1990 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - The Illusion of Prosperity: New York in the New Economy - Fiscal Policy Institute Publication, 1999 September (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Kraft General Foods Grant Submission, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Mary Jo Bane, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Media Lists and Thank you Letters from the Development Director, 1991 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Military Spending, 1989-1992 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Military Spending, 1989-1992; 1994 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Mohawk-Hudson Community Foundation, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Multilateral Agreement on Investment (MAI), 1997 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Negatives, Undated (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - NYS Census of Population and Housing, 1990 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - NYS Department of Social Services Social Statistics, 1985-1990; 1992-1994 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - NYS Department of Social Services Social Statistics, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - NYS Department of Social Services Social Statistics, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - NYS Office of Temporary and Disability Assistance Proposals of Establishing the Transitional Oppurtunities Program, 2000 June 12 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - NYS Office of Temporary and Disability Assistance Statistics, 1997 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - NYS Office of Temporary and Disability Assistance Statistics [1 of 2], 1998 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - NYS Office of Temporary and Disability Assistance Statistics [2 of 2], 1998 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - NYS Office of Temporary and Disability Assistance Statistics, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - NYS Office of Temporary and Disability Assistance Statistics, 2000 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - NYS Office of Temporary and Disability Assistance Statistics, 2001 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Other Hunger Organizations Newsletters, Undated (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Post-Employment Education and Training Models in the Welfare to Work Grants, 1999 May (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Presiding Bishop Fund for World Relief Grant Materials, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Newsletters of Other Organizations, 1985-1988; 1991-1992; 1999 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Nontraditional Employment for Women, 2000 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Regional Food Bank Extra Helpings: A Community Food Buying Club, 1999; Undated (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Regional Food Bank of Northeastern New York, 2002 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Rensselaer County IDA, 2000 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Resource Room Packet, 2001 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Rochester Empower, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - The Society of Association Executives of Upstate New York 1991 Members (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Strategic Fundraising Workshop, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Summer Reception for the Long Island Office of HANNYS Invitation and Guest List, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Summer Food Service Program, 1990-1992; 1998-1999 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Summer Food Service Program, 1994; 1997 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Summer Food Service Program, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Thanksgiving Fast to End Hunger, 1995 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Thanksgiving Fast to End Hunger, 1996; 1997 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Thanksgiving Fast to End Hunger, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Thanksgiving Fast to End Hunger, 1999 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Thanksgiving Fast to End Hunger, 2000 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Thanksgiving Fast to End Hunger, 2001 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Thanksgiving Fast to End Hunger, 2002 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF) Fact Sheets, 2000; Undated (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Transitional Oppurtunities Program (TOP), 2000; 2001 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - T-Shirts/ Screen Designs, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Welfare, AFDC, 1991; Undated (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Welfare Dilemmas, 2000 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Welfare Employment, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 31)